Dincer Tezcan

Praha 1, CZ +420 774 492 944 Dincertezcan@hotmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/dincer-tezcan

My career started at Accenture as analyst. I worked for various clients and projects as Technical support and first point of contact for clients. Main responsibility was ERP implementation for clients and building / maintaining their database and helping them thru execution of ERP systems. As in Software development life cycle, I participated in "Analysis of requirements" to assist clients as well as developers to identify needs and modify their system or application accordingly and "System functionality testing" to verify if the functionality and the behavior of the system or application meets the requirements including manual black-box testing and white-box testing. Those were mostly ERP Quoting and Contracting modules, Finance and Accounting modules, e-invoicing modules. I prepared documentations and trainings of systems, processes and tools for knowledge transfer to either clients or internal shared service centers.

Skills

- Python programming language Proficient
- Web development / HTML, CSS Proficient
- SQL / Relational Database Proficient
- JavaScript programming language Familiar
- Selenium testing framework Familiar
- ERP systems and applications

Language

- Turkish as Native
- English as Fluent C2
- Czech as Intermediate A1

Experience

AUG 2017 - MAR 2020

Contract system specialist / Oracle Corporation, Praha, CZ

- Deal-contract specialist for Hardware and Database systems.
- Systems specialist for ERPs` contracting modules.
- System and data maintenance. Contract drafting.
- Technical support for various departments as Sales, Legal and Finance.
- Data maintenance. Managing master data. Provide quality assurance of imported data.

Systems Specialist / Accenture, Praha, CZ

- Implement new systems or upgrade existing system.
- Installing and configuring new technologies to be used by end users.
- Assisting staff with data entry methods and usage of systems.
- Acting as an information source and system support for end users.

SEP 2011 - NOV 2015

Analyst at Business Outsourcing Operation / Accenture, Praha, CZ

- Quality Assurance analysis and testing.
- Knowledge Transfer in Service Provider Transition.
- Implementation and testing of ERP systems and applications.
- Monitoring and maintenance of client systems and database.
- Modifying systems, processes as per end user requirements.
- Creating documentations and giving trainings to clients or internal back-office.

Education

2006 - 2010

Bachelor's Degree / Jan Amos Komensky University, CZ

European Economic and Social Studies. http://www.ujak.cz/

2001 - 2004

High School - Gymnasium / Mehmet Çelikel Anadolu Lisesi - TED Zonguldak Koleji, TR

Major in Mathematics and Physics. https://www.ted.org.tr

Hobbies and Interests

- Tech in all aspects.
- Programming and coding.
- Reading. Preferably Non-fictions.
- Drawing things. Not painting!

- Video gaming. Not like an addict.
- Films and Movies. Like an addict.
- Music. I am learning drumming.
- Rafting and table football semi pro